{
    "subject": "resource/El_Topo",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1970_films",
    "human_readable": "El Topo is a subject of 1970 films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.878557562828064,
            "question": "Is El Topo the subject of a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6759942173957825,
            "question": "In what decade was El Topo featured in films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6584537625312805,
            "question": "What genre are the films about El Topo likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6530792117118835,
            "question": "What year were films about El Topo released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6357875466346741,
            "question": "Could El Topo be a character in a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6193503141403198,
            "question": "Have the films about El Topo received critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5853894352912903,
            "question": "Are there any films featuring El Topo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5686225295066833,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in films featuring El Topo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.553675651550293,
            "question": "What other information can we learn about El Topo from these films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4105350375175476,
            "question": "Are there any famous directors who have made films about El Topo?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=El Topo is a subject of 1970 films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2790_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other information can we learn about El Topo from these films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2790_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes might be explored in films featuring El Topo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2790_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any films featuring El Topo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2790_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2790_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents discuss the film \"El Topo,\" which was released in 1970, thus supporting the statement that \"El Topo\" is a subject of 1970 films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}